<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ghour</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!--Dropdwon menu for authority work-->
    <string-array name="works">
        <item>Select your work</item>
        <item>Police</item>
        <item>Doctor</item>
        <item>Firefighter</item>
        <item>Social Worker</item>
        <item>NGO</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Dropdown meny for all join-->
    <string-array name="all_works">
        <item>Select your work</item>
        <item>User</item>
        <item>Police</item>
        <item>Doctor</item>
        <item>Firefighter</item>
        <item>Social Worker</item>
        <item>NGO</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="saved_message">Image Saved at %1$s</string>
    <string name="accident">ACCIDENT</string>
    <string name="fire">FIRE</string>
    <string name="tsunami">TSUNAMI</string>
    <string name="flood">FLOOD</string>
    <string name="earthquake">EARTHQUAKE</string>

    <string name="WhattoDoBeforeanEarthquake">Repair deep plaster cracks in ceilings and foundations. Get expert advice if there are signs of structural defects.
Anchor overhead lighting fixtures to the ceiling.
Follow BIS codes relevant to your area for building standards
Fasten shelves securely to walls.
Place large or heavy objects on lower shelves.
Store breakable items such as bottled foods, glass, and china in low, closed cabinets with latches.
Hang heavy items such as pictures and mirrors away from beds, settees, and anywhere that people sit.
Brace overhead light and fan fixtures.
Repair defective electrical wiring and leaky gas connections. These are potential fire risks.
Secure water heaters, LPG cylinders etc., by strapping them to the walls or bolting to the floor.
Store weed killers, pesticides, and flammable products securely in closed cabinets with latches and on bottom shelves.
Identify safe places indoors and outdoors.
Under strong dining table, bed
Against an inside wall
Away from where glass could shatter around windows, mirrors, pictures, or where heavy bookcases or other heavy furniture could fall over
In the open, away from buildings, trees, telephone and electrical lines, flyovers and bridges
Know emergency telephone numbers (such as those of doctors, hospitals, the police, etc)
Educate yourself and family members

</string>


</resources>
